[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
We've learned now, together, we've learned two regression models from our data,
我们已经学习了 通过两种不同的模型来训练我们的数据
one just based on square foot of living,
第一个模型仅仅使用了房屋面积这个特征
the other one based on these more advanced features.
第二个模型使用了更多更详细的特征
So let's apply these models.
让我们来运用这些模型
Let's see what it looks like when we use them in practice to predict house prices.
让我们来看怎么实际操作来预测房屋价格
So, what we're going to do is apply this learned
我们要做的是把我们训练的模型
models to predict prices of three houses from
去预测3个数据中的房屋的价格
the data set, so three different houses.
三个不同的房屋
So the first house is, and this is three that I picked
第一个房屋是
that had different sizes, different properties,
他们有着不同的 房屋面积 不同的性质
they look a bit different, in different neighborhoods.
他们看起来也不同 也处于不同的小区位置
So let's just look at them.
让我们先看一下
So the first house is from our data and
第一个来自我们data这个数据中的房屋时
so what we're gonna do with this house is, so this is for not data but sales data.
我们要做的就是  额这个数据其实不是来自于data 而是来自于销售数据（sales data）（教授把两个数据来源记错名字了）
So out of my sales data, I'm going to
在我们的销售数据中
select the house whose id is equal to a particular id.
我要去选一个房屋 它的ID（代码）会是一个特定的ID （代码）
And so the county record gives us string ids for every house, it gives a number.
所以说 记录给了我们每一个房子的id 这是一串数字
So this one is 5309, I'm copying from a piece of paper here, 101200.
第一个房子的id 是5309 是101200
So, a particular house for a particular id, and so I'm selecting it
所以说每一个房子都有着自己的ID 我们现在正在选择
and if I type house1, you'll see what it is.
对于房屋1 你会看到
So it's the house that has this particular ID.
这就是这个id 房子的数据
It got sold on this date for $620,000.
它卖了620000美元
It had four bedrooms, two and
它有着四个卧室
a quarter bathrooms, 2,400 square feet of living space, and so on.
两个卫生间 2400平方尺的居住空间 等等等等
Now what you can do is in iPython notebook,
接下来要在Python Notebook 做的就是
you can embed not only mark ups and texts in the Python code.
我们不光可以在里面放置Python的代码 文本
But you can also embed HTML and images.
还可以在notebook中插入HTML和图片
So let me just do that for you right now, just as an example.
我们来给你举个例子
So I'm typing xm and then I am going to add an image to my notebook and this image
我在输入xm 我会添加一个图片在Notebook(笔记本中） 这个图片
is an image that I downloaded from the county records for this particular house.
是我从郡记录哪里下载的 某一个房子的照片
So, the image is on my directory, it's called house.
这个图片正在我的路径中 叫做房屋
So, house, 53, what was the number?
53个房子 它的ID是什么
09101200, so this is gonna be pretty cool.
噢是09101200 非常完美
When I see a picture of the house we're trying to make a prediction for, oops,
当我看到房子的照片的时候 我们即将要预测 噢糟了
I must have typed that wrong oh, yeah.
我输错了
I forgot it's .jpg.
我忘记了 这个照片的格式是.jpg
And that's pretty cool, here's a picture of the house we're pricing.
恩现在好了 这就是我们要预测价格的房屋照片
So this house was sold in 2014 for $620,000.
这个房子在2014年卖了620000
It has four bedrooms, two and a quarter bathrooms.
四个卧室 两个卫生间
It was built, for example, in 1929.
1929年造的
Now, let's see what our model predicts.
我们可以看我们模型预测的价格是多少
So, We had two models.
我们有两个模型
So, we had first.
第一个模型
So the true price of the house.
恩这个房子的价格是
And just a print out to remind ourselves, so this is house1 of price.
让我们打印出来以免忘记 这就是房屋1的售价
This is 200 so if I just type print here, it will look a little nicer.
恩200（口误） 我就直接打印出来 看起来更清楚
$620,000, this is the house price.
恩房屋售价是620000
Then let's see what my first model predicts.
让我们看看第一个模型预测的价格
So that was the simple square foot model that we built.
这是一个简单的只用了房屋面积这个特征的模型
When you they it, so whenI typed .predict,
我现在输入predict
the price of house1, and it says it predicts it as
房屋1的售价 第一个模型告诉我们
$628,000, so pretty close, actually.
它的售价是628000 恩非常接近真实售价
That's really good.
完美
And let's see what adding more features did for us.
那我们看看添加了更多特征的第二个模型吧
my_features_model.predict:house1, so
my_feature_model.predict（house1） 输入这个指令
you remember on average, the my features model,
你要记住 普遍情况下 越多的特征被添加进模型
adding more features, gives you better performance.
你会得到更好的结果
Now, if you look at the prediction here, it's $720,000, so the square
但是你看到它给出的预测是720000
foot model had a better prediction than the one with more features.
所以说第一个模型比第二个有着更多的特征的模型 有着更好的预测结果
So what we learned here is, even though on average,
所以我们这里学到的是 在通常情况下
adding more features give a better prediction.
添加更多的特征会有这更好的预测结果
For this one particular house,
但是对于某一个特定的房屋
the simple model did a better job than the more advanced model.
简单的模型反而会比复杂的模型来的更好
But this is to be expected, and not always, but
不过我们所预期的是 有着更多特征的模型
sometimes gonna do better, probably works, when average is going to do better.
有时候会更好 普遍情况下会更好
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community